Enter Subject Number (followed by Enter or Return):
Press Space Bar to Begin Practice
Press Space Bar to Begin Task
Press Space Bar to Continue With Next Trial
Press Space Bar After Break
Task over: Press Space Bar to Proceed to Next Task
Wait... sentences being read
Experiment over: Call Experimenter
Press Space to Continue
Data Recorded - Press Space Bar to Exit
Please Draw the Dots
Next
End
nix
Block Accomplished - Press Space Bar to Continue With Next Block
Please wait … word being read
